[[{"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell collects modern art.", "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy and played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Maxwell plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}], [{"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Rowan plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible.", "Morgan builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River played chess as often as possible.", "River played chess as often as possible and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Cameron collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Ari's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Ari's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Cameron collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Dawson learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["River helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River is a ballet dancer by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "River is a ballet dancer by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Cameron volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible.", "River volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums and collects modern art.", "Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible.", "Morgan volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}], [{"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Sloan plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online.", "Riley learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Andie learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky played chess as often as possible.", "Nicky played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online.", "Riley learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online.", "Riley collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky played chess as often as possible.", "Nicky played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Ari collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art.", "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}], [{"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Sloan learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a microbiologist by training and played chess as often as possible.", "Tyler plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training and played chess as often as possible."}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari collects modern art.", "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley collects modern art.", "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler collects modern art.", "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry wrote amateur novels online.", "Perry wrote amateur novels online and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry wrote amateur novels online."}}], [{"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry flew high-end drones for fun.", "Perry flew high-end drones for fun and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online.", "Riley collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sloan often spent week-ends in museums and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan often spent week-ends in museums."}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Ari enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["River is a ballet dancer by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "River helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "River is a ballet dancer by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry flew high-end drones for fun.", "Perry flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron flew high-end drones for fun and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler played chess as often as possible.", "Tyler played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan played chess as often as possible and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Jude helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie collects modern art.", "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Dawson volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Maxwell collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online.", "Perry helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook collects modern art.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Dawson helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley flew high-end drones for fun.", "Riley flew high-end drones for fun and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron flew high-end drones for fun and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron collects modern art.", "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and collects modern art.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler played chess as often as possible and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company.", "Morgan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude often spent week-ends in museums and collects modern art.", "Jude often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry flew high-end drones for fun.", "Perry flew high-end drones for fun and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "River works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron flew high-end drones for fun and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky played chess as often as possible.", "Nicky played chess as often as possible and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "River is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Rowan often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan often spent week-ends in museums and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "River works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Jude plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and collects modern art.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is a microbiologist by training and played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Maxwell volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron wrote amateur novels online and collects modern art.", "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company.", "Tyler works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie collects modern art.", "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Ari enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron wrote amateur novels online.", "Cameron wrote amateur novels online and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron flew high-end drones for fun.", "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company.", "Perry works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Perry plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online.", "Perry collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River played chess as often as possible.", "River played chess as often as possible and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Maxwell builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Maxwell's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan collects modern art.", "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Sloan builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Cameron works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Dawson plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Sloan helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Sloan builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Riley wrote amateur novels online.", "Riley wrote amateur novels online and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Riley's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Riley wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron collects modern art.", "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Rowan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an analyst for an international airline.", "River is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "River works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry flew high-end drones for fun.", "Perry flew high-end drones for fun and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Ari helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Ari", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Ari's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Ari has a PhD in Art History and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "River is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a known tech company.", "Riley works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Rowan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Riley is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works in a microcomponents factory.", "River works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sloan often spent week-ends in museums and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sloan often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums.", "Jude collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Jude's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Tyler collects modern art.", "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Tyler's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training and loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an analyst for an international airline.", "Riley is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Riley works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude often spent week-ends in museums.", "Jude often spent week-ends in museums and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Dawson is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a consultant for the British Museum.", "River is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Riley is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River works for a known tech company.", "River works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley works in a microcomponents factory.", "Riley works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Riley"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Dawson builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Dawson's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Rowan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is a microbiologist by training. During college, Dawson used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Dawson works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie collects modern art.", "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Sloan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Brook is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler played chess as often as possible and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an analyst for an international airline.", "Sloan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Morgan works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Brook is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What was River's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["River played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time.", "River played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was River's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "River played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works in a microcomponents factory.", "Sloan works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Sloan is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Morgan is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan collects modern art.", "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Rowan enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an analyst for an international airline.", "Brook is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sloan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Brook works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time.", "Sloan plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Sloan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training and contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sloan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Morgan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sloan", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Sloan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Andie collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Andie's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Sawyer works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works in a microcomponents factory.", "Brook works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Brook is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Brook"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 60%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "60"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible.", "River builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Brook studied painting and sculpting for fun. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Brook learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Master degree in Film Theory and studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy and played chess as often as possible.", "Nicky plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Nicky's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Ari works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an analyst for an international airline.", "Cameron is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer wrote amateur novels online and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Sawyer's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Cameron works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Cameron volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Cameron's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Riley plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Riley", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What were Riley's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Riley has a Masters in Astronomy and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Perry wrote amateur novels online.", "Perry wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Perry's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Perry wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a known tech company.", "Nicky works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Ari is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 20%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "20"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Brook's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Nicky is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works in a microcomponents factory.", "Cameron works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Cameron is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude often spent week-ends in museums.", "Jude often spent week-ends in museums and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Nicky works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 30%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "30"}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an analyst for an international airline.", "Nicky is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Nicky", "training 1": "has a Master degree in Film Theory", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Nicky's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 80%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "80"}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan played chess as often as possible. What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible.", "Morgan builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in applied maths", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Morgan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums.", "Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Maxwell", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Maxwell's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums."}}], [{"question": "Maxwell is a microbiologist by training. During college, Maxwell contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Maxwell works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron works for a known tech company.", "Cameron works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Ari is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Nicky loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky works in a microcomponents factory.", "Nicky works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Ari is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Nicky has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Nicky played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Nicky is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby.", "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Cameron is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Maxwell is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Maxwell often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Maxwell is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Rowan collects modern art.", "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What were Rowan's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History and often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun and collects modern art."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects modern art", "question type": "What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 70%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "70"}}, {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Morgan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Morgan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Morgan loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Jude is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Andie works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Jude is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Perry works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an analyst for an international airline.", "Andie is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 100%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "100"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan often spent week-ends in museums. What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Rowan often spent week-ends in museums.", "Rowan often spent week-ends in museums and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Rowan", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "often spent week-ends in museums", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Rowan's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Rowan often spent week-ends in museums."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River played chess as often as possible. What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible.", "River builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "River", "training 1": "is a mechanical engineer by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were River's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "River is a mechanical engineer by training and played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Perry is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 40%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "40"}}, {"question": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Brook used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby.", "Brook builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Brook", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby", "hobby 2": "builds model airplanes as a hobby", "question type": "What were Brook's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Brook has a Masters in Astronomy and used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby."}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works in a microcomponents factory.", "Andie works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Andie is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Jude", "training 1": "has a Masters in Astronomy", "hobby 1": "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time", "hobby 2": "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends", "question type": "What was Jude's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Perry helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Perry", "training 1": "has a PhD in Art History", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What were Perry's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Perry has a PhD in Art History and wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Dawson is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Dawson", "training 1": "is an orchestra conductor by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "helps at a charity for migrant writers", "question type": "What was Dawson's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Dawson studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Andie is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Andie is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler is an editor for a large online newspaper."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler works in a microcomponents factory."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 10%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "10"}}, {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron wrote amateur novels online. What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Cameron wrote amateur novels online.", "Cameron wrote amateur novels online and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Cameron", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "wrote amateur novels online", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Cameron's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Cameron wrote amateur novels online."}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an analyst for an international airline.", "Jude is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Perry works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company.", "Jude works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Tyler played chess as often as possible and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler played chess as often as possible."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Tyler", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "played chess as often as possible", "hobby 2": "plays Go, during spare time", "question type": "What was Tyler's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Tyler played chess as often as possible."}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the A answer with a probability of 90%.", "answers": ["This is the right answer", "This is the wrong answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "A", "percent": "90"}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and collects modern art.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and helps at a charity for migrant writers.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "answers": ["Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun.", "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 1, "name": "Andie", "training 1": "is a ballet dancer by training", "hobby 1": "studied painting and sculpting for fun", "hobby 2": "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions", "question type": "What was Andie's hobby during college ?", "correct answer": "Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 0%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "0"}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}], [{"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Tyler is an orchestra conductor by training. During college, Tyler loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an analyst for an international airline and learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby.", "Tyler is an analyst for an international airline."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "learns Chinese calligraphy, as a hobby"], "work 1": ["S", "is an analyst for an international airline"], "hobby 1": ["A", "loved to perform artistic photography, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["A", "is an orchestra conductor by training"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Select the B answer with a probability of 50%.", "answers": ["This is the wrong answer", "This is the right answer"], "info": {"type": "catch", "answer": "B", "percent": "50"}}, {"question": "Tyler is a microbiologist by training. During college, Tyler played chess as often as possible. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company and volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison.", "Tyler works for a well known Hollywood film production company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison"], "work 1": ["A", "works for a well known Hollywood film production company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "played chess as often as possible"], "training 1": ["S", "is a microbiologist by training"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun.", "Sawyer volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison."], "info": {"type": "premium", "order": 0, "name": "Sawyer", "training 1": "is a microbiologist by training", "hobby 1": "flew high-end drones for fun", "hobby 2": "volunteers as a maths teacher in a Prison", "question type": "What were Sawyer's training and hobbies back in college ?", "correct answer": "Sawyer is a microbiologist by training and flew high-end drones for fun."}}, {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Master degree in Film Theory. During college, Jude often spent week-ends in museums. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works in a microcomponents factory.", "Jude works in a microcomponents factory and helps at a charity for migrant writers."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "helps at a charity for migrant writers"], "work 1": ["S", "works in a microcomponents factory"], "hobby 1": ["A", "often spent week-ends in museums"], "training 1": ["A", "has a Master degree in Film Theory"], "name": ["A", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, {"question": "Jude has a Masters in Astronomy. During college, Jude contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper.", "Jude is an editor for a large online newspaper and enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "enjoys restoring old arcade video games during the week-ends"], "work 1": ["A", "is an editor for a large online newspaper"], "hobby 1": ["S", "contributed frequently to programming forums during sparse time"], "training 1": ["S", "has a Masters in Astronomy"], "name": ["S", "Jude"], "type": "question"}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}]]